[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What Academy Award-winning director worked on the 1980 movie Raging Bull, voted the best sports movie of all time by the American Film Institute?", "correct_answer": "Martin Scorsese", "incorrect_answers": ["Quentin Tarantino", "Stanley Kubrick", "Oliver Stone"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the subject of study of paleoanthropology?", "correct_answer": "ancient human  fossils", "incorrect_answers": ["the earliest human discoveries and accomplishments", "older people", "old cultures and societies"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is Kates fiance in the 2007 movie Norbit?", "correct_answer": "Deion Hughes", "incorrect_answers": ["Norbit Rice", "Rob Just", "Buster"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was on the boat in Echo Park with Hollis I. Mulwray in the film Chinatown?", "correct_answer": "Katherine Cross", "incorrect_answers": ["Ida Sessions", "Sophie", "Evelyn Cross Mulwray"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which planet was named after the Roman god of war?", "correct_answer": "Mars", "incorrect_answers": ["Uranus", "Mercury", "Saturn"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Coq Au Vin is a typical dish for this country, and it is prepared in all its regions, though with slight changes in recipe. It is a kind of chicken stew.", "correct_answer": "France", "incorrect_answers": ["Belgium", "Germany", "Switzerland"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The painting Mona Lisa by Leonardo da Vinci was stolen on August 21, 1911.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does the scientific name of the King cobra, Ophiophagus, mean?", "correct_answer": "Snake eater", "incorrect_answers": ["Royal snake", "Elephant killer", "Deadly reptile"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This orange vegetable was first discovered in Afghanistan 5000 years ago. Paintings were found on the walls of temples in Egypt, where it is believed to have been used for  treatment of diseases.", "correct_answer": "Carrot", "incorrect_answers": ["Tomato", "Pumpkin", "Broccoli"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The first product to have a bar code was this.", "correct_answer": "Gum", "incorrect_answers": ["Oil", "Flour", "Wine"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What 1992 movie contains the quote, You are not content with the stories, so I was obliged to come.?", "correct_answer": "Candyman", "incorrect_answers": ["The Nightmare on Elm Street", "Leprechaun", "Buried Alive"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "On this TV show the lawyers shingle reads Attorney-at-Law, Ernest Frye - Where Winning Is Everything.", "correct_answer": "Amen", "incorrect_answers": ["Arrest and Trial", "The Antagonists", "Any Day Now"]}]